In days of legend,
在传说时代
gods walked the Earth...
神明在凡间穿巡....
and tormented mortals.
摧残凡人
Athena, goddess of warfare and wisdom,
雅典娜, 战争与智慧之女神
had the power to destroy humanity,
明明拥有毁灭人类的力量,
but chose to protect us.
却选择了保护我们
Brave young knights from across the globe
来自世界各地的勇敢的年轻圣斗士们
swore their allegiance to her.N宣誓效忠于她
They learned to harness Cosmo...
他们学会了驾驭小宇宙....
the power of the stars.
星辰的力量
Their fists cracked to the heavens
他们的拳头划破了云霄
in battles against those who wished Athena dead.
在与那些意图杀害雅典娜的敌人的战斗中
Over time...
星转斗移....
the gods retreated and became myths.
众神退隐, 成为神话
But then, 18 years ago,
但是, 18 年前,
Athena was reborn as a helpless child.
雅典娜获得重生 成了一个无助的婴儿
A knight clad in gold armor
一名黄金圣斗士
gave his life to protect her as they crashed to Earth.
在他们坠落到凡间之时, 献出生命保护了她
And that's how I found her, lying in his arms.
就这样 我发现了她 躺在他怀里
A mortal girl with the power of a god.
一个拥有神之力量的凡人女孩
Since then,
从那时起
I've been searching for a new generation of knights
我就一直在寻找新一代的圣斗士
to protect Athena and the Earth.
来保护雅典娜和地球
《圣斗士星矢》
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的
We fight to protect ourselves.
我们是为了保护自己而战斗
But we also fight to protect each other.
但我们也是为了保护彼此而战斗
There's always something bigger than you, Seiya.
还有比你自己更重要的东西, 星矢
You'll have to fight to protect that as well.
你也必须为了保护它而战斗
You give up?
你投降了？
Never!
绝不！
Nice try. But not tonight.
干的漂亮 但今晚不行
- Tap out. - No!
- 认输 - 不
You must learn when to quit!
你必须学会何时放弃！
Never!
绝不！
No, Seiya! Don't!
不 星矢 不要
Promise you won't come out.
答应我 你别出来
I promise.
我保证
Hey, kid!
嘿, 孩子
Come on, you're up next.
来吧, 你是下一个
You win this fight, maybe you get a shot at me someday.
你赢了这场比赛, 说不定哪天就能和我一决高下了
Hey! Listen to me.
嘿 听我说
No more of that dancing around, you understand?
别再跳来跳去了, 明白吗？
You make it a good show this time.
你可要好好表现这次
Fight this time, asshole.
这次好好打, 混蛋
It's time for the main event!
重头戏来了
Introducing first, the undisputed champion of the Octagon.
首先出场的是无可争议的八角笼冠军
Give it up for Jaki the Beast!
为野兽贾基鼓掌！
Jaki! Jaki! Jaki!
贾基！贾基！贾基！
And the contender, who literally danced his way
而这位竞争者, 简直就是靠跳舞
to through his first two fights,
通过了前两场比赛
let's hear it for Street Kid Seiya!
让我们为街头小子星矢欢呼！
You both know how this works.
你们都知道这是什么地方
You know the rules. There are none.
你们知道规则 就是没有规则
Anything goes until one of you gives up or blacks out.
任何招式都可以, 直到你们其中一个投降或昏倒
If you give up, you're banished from the Octagon.
如果你投降, 就会被逐出八角笼
Understood?
明白了吗？
Damn it, fight!
该死的, 打啊！
Hey! I said, no dancing!
我说了, 不许跳舞
Cassios! Cassios! Cassios!
卡西欧士 卡西欧士 卡西欧士
What, you think you can just ignore me?
怎么, 你以为你可以无视我？
Okay, calm down, big guy.
好了, 冷静点, 大个子
Ballet's over, kid.
芭蕾结束了, 孩子
Cassios wins.
卡西欧士赢了
Every...
每...
single...
一...
time.
次
Cassios! Cassios! Cassios!
卡西欧士 卡西欧士 卡西欧士
You give up?
你投降了？
Yeah!
耶
You don't know when to quit, huh?
你不知道什么时候该投降, 是吧？
Yeah.
是啊
I've heard that before.
我以前就听说过
We're not done here!
我们还没完！
This ain't over!
这还没完！
Come outside.
到外面来
You're cute, but you're not my type, man.
你很可爱, 但不是我喜欢的类型, 伙计
There's someone outside that wants to speak with you.
外面有人想和你聊聊
He knows about your search.
他知道你在找人
He knows what you're looking for.
他知道你在找什么
Give me that.
给我
Yeah, it's me.
是我
Think I found one of your Cosmo guys.
我想我发现了一个你要的圣斗士
I'm out of here.
我要走了
Your little show in there made some people upset.
你在那里的小表演让一些人不高兴了
Look, I'm not looking for trouble.
听着, 我不是来找麻烦的
You may not be looking, but you've found it.
也许你不是, 但麻烦已经找到你了
In a few moments, Vander Guraad will be here with her boys.
再过几分钟, 范德·古拉杜就会带着她的手下们来了
Who?
谁？
My ex- wife.
我的前妻
She controls this fighting ring.
她控制着这个格斗场
It's her recruitment operation.
这是她的招集障眼法
What do you mean? What does she recruit?
什么意思？招集什么？
Warriors with special skills.
拥有特殊技能的战士
For her private army.
组建她的私人军队
Okay.
好吧
I saw what you did in the ring.
我看到了你在擂台上的表现
I knew it had to be you, Seiya.
我就知道一定是你, 星矢
Who are you?
你是谁？
I'm the only friend you have.
我是你唯一的朋友
You need to make a choice, Seiya.
你得做个选择了, 星矢
Come with me or try your luck against Guraad's warriors.
跟我走, 要不就跟古拉杜的战士们碰碰运气
Lead the way.
带路
Come on!
来吧
Look what we've found.
看看我们发现了什么
What are those guys made of?
那些家伙是什么做的？
You don't want to know. Keep moving!
你不会想知道的 继续走
Our ride's just around the corner!
我们的接应就在街角
Get down!
趴下
Go!
走
Meet Mylock, my assistant.
这是晨己, 我的助手
Those guys work for your ex- wife?
那些家伙是给你前妻工作的？
Surrender the boy!
交出那小子
Dude, you gotta make better life choices.
老兄, 你该选一个更好的老婆
What the hell is that thing?
那到底是什么东西？
Hope you had a light dinner.
希望你晚上吃得不多
Why are they after me?
他们为什么要抓我？
They're after warriors with a strong Cosmo.
他们要抓的是拥有强大小宇宙的战士
Cosmo? Is that a new martial arts or something?
小宇宙？那是一种新门派还是什么？
You should know. You tapped into it in the Octagon.
你应该知道 你在八角笼里就已经觉醒过了
I didn't tap into anything. They got the wrong guy!
我什么也没有觉醒过 他们抓错人了
Oh, would you like us to stop and let them know?
哦, 你想停下来告诉他们吗？
God!
上帝啊
Hold on tight!
抓紧了
I am not going another step until you tell me what's going on.
除非你告诉我发生了什么事, 不然我不会再走一步了
There'll be time for that later.
以后有得是时间告诉你
We're still in danger.
我们还没脱离危险
You're really...
你真的...
Okay, okay, okay. Go to sleep.
好吧 睡吧
Hey. Hey. Wake up. Wake up.
嘿 醒醒
Wake up. Come on.
醒醒 快来
You need to hide. No matter what happens, you stay out of sight.
你要躲起来 无论发生什么 都不要出来
I have to make sure these people don't find you.
我必须确保这些人不会找到你
Promise you won't come out.
答应我你别出来
Okay. I promise.
好的 我保证
Thank you.
谢谢
For what?
为了什么？
You tapped into your Cosmo.
你觉醒了你的小宇宙
No, Seiya. Don't!
不 星矢 不要
Led me right to your doorstep.
指引我到了你家门口
检测到能量资源
目标
Saved me so much trouble.
给我省了很多麻烦
Let's go!
我们走吧
You can't use it. Only the Pegasus can!
你用不了的 只有天马座才可以
That's why you're coming with us.
这就是为什么你要跟我们走
Relax.
放松
Relax, we're safe now.
放松, 我们现在安全了
Safe?
安全？
First I get attacked by ninja cyborgs,
我先被忍者机器人袭击
then I got a spaceship shooting at me.
然后就有一艘飞船朝我开火
And then that freak in a suit drugs me!
再然后那个穿西装的怪胎给我下了药
Allow me to rephrase it.
请允许我换一种说法
You're safer here than with Guraad.
你在这里会比跟着古拉杜更安全
She has already captured many kids like you,
她已经抓走了很多像你一样的孩子
drained them of their Cosmo.
吸干了他们的小宇宙
Stop talking nonsense and tell me what's going on!
别再胡说八道了, 告诉我到底怎么回事！
- Prepare for landing. - What?
- 准备着陆 - 什么？
You might want to buckle up.
你最好系好安全带
No, I want answers now!
不, 我现在就要答案！
Oh, shit.
哦, 该死
There's no runway!
没跑道啊
I said, you might want to buckle up.
我说过, 你最好系上安全带
You couldn't just tell me this thing lands vertically?
你就不能告诉我这东西是垂直降落的吗？
Let's start afresh, shall we?
让我们重新开始, 好吗？
My name is Alman Kido.
我叫城户光政
Once upon a time, I was a businessman.
从前, 我是一个商人
Mylock, let her know our guest has arrived, please.
晨己, 请告诉她我们的客人到了
Yes, sir.
是的, 先生
Should I believe you went bust?
我应该相信你破产了吗？
I won't hide the fact I've been quite successful in my trade.
不瞒你说, 我的生意做得相当成功
But the one thing money can't buy is purpose.
但有一样东西是金钱买不到的, 那就是使命
So this is where you store your "purpose"?
这就是你存放"使命"的地方？
Yes.
是的
Tell me, Seiya, what do you see?
告诉我, 星矢, 你看到了什么？
I'm not sure.
我不确定
A whole bunch of real old stuff, I guess.
一大堆真正的古董 我猜
I see stories.
我看到的是故事
Ancient heroes were defined by their monumental deeds
古代英雄是由他们的不朽事迹
as much as by their tragic ends.
和他们的悲剧结局所定义的
I always admired the formidable magnitude of their fate.
我一直钦佩他们命运的伟大
I envied it. I used to think the ancient lore held no secret for me.
我很羡慕 我曾经以为古老的传说对我来说没有什么秘密
I'm afraid that was my hubris.
恐怕是我太傲慢了
What do you know about Athena?
你对雅典娜了解多少？
- She was a god of war. - And wisdom.
- 她是战争之神 - 也是智慧之神
What if I told you Athena had returned in human form
如果我告诉你 雅典娜重回人间了
and you are destined to become one of her guardian knights?
而你注定要成为她的守护圣斗士之一呢？
I'd say your therapist isn't worth his paycheck.
我得说, 你的心理医生配不上你付他的薪水
Things happen for a reason, Seiya.
事出必有因, 星矢
Your Cosmo brought you here.
是你的小宇宙把你带到这里来的
Actually, I was brought here on a very expensive aircraft.
事实上, 我是乘坐一架非常昂贵的飞机来的
And now I'm leaving on my own two feet.
现在, 我要靠自己的双脚离开了
You know the truth in your heart, Seiya.
你心底知道真相, 星矢
Your sister knew it too.
你姐姐也知道
What do you know about my sister?
你对我姐姐了解多少？
Ten years ago,
Guraad detected a strong Cosmo
at your location. She thought it was Patricia.
在你家那里 她以为是星华
What did she do to her?
她对她做了什么？
I don't know, but your sister gave herself up
我不知道, 但你姐姐拿自己顶上了
so that Guraad wouldn't find you.
这样古拉杜就不会去找你
She knew what you were to become.
她知道你的天命所归
A warrior of Athena. The Pegasus Knight.
雅典娜的战士 天马座圣斗士
The Pegasus Knight?
天马座圣斗士？
You're really out of your mind.
你真是疯了
That doesn't bode well.
这可不是什么好兆头
This is Sienna.
这是沙织
Guraad is after her too.
古拉杜也在追杀她
Your mission is to protect her.
你的任务是保护她
I can take care of myself.
我能照顾好自己
Why would I ever want to risk my neck to protect some rich girl?
我为什么要冒着生命危险去保护一个富家千金？
Because our little Sienna here is the reincarnation of the goddess Athena.
因为我们的小沙织就是雅典娜女神转世
- Dad. - Don't you have something for our guest?
- 爸爸 - 你不是有东西要给我们的客人吗？
Sure, a toilet, so he can flush himself out.
当然, 给个厕所, 这样他就能把自己冲走了
Wow, spoken like a true goddess.
哇, 说得像个真正的女神
Dad, come on. This moron can't seriously be the Pegasus Knight.
爸爸, 别这样，这个白痴不可能真的是天马座圣斗士
Go on.
去吧
Fine.
很好
You might recognize this, Seiya.
你可能认得这个, 星矢
This is Patricia's.
这是星华的
That is the key to the Pegasus armor.
这就是天马圣衣的钥匙
Without it, you don't stand a chance against Guraad's army.
没有圣衣, 想要对抗古拉杜的大军, 你根本没有机会
I could've handled those guys.
我可以对付那些家伙
That's not what Mylock said.
晨己可不是这么说的
So how's this supposed to help me find my sister?
这个要怎么才能帮我找到我姐姐？
You give me a little present and expect me to help you out?
给我一个小礼物, 就指望我会帮你？
My plan is to trust you to do what is right.
我的计划是相信你会做正确的事
And what would that be?
那是什么呢？
I suppose you've never heard of Marin, the Silver Knight.
我想你从未听说过白银圣斗士魔铃吧
God, another one of your old legends?
天哪, 又一个你的古老传说？
Marin can teach you how to reveal
魔铃可以教你如何揭示
the hidden secret of the pendant.
那个吊坠的秘密
So you can protect Sienna, and yourself, against your enemies.
这样你就能保护沙织, 和你自己, 对抗敌人
And maybe even help you find your sister.
也许还能帮你找到你姐姐
Ancient gods. Magic knights.
古代诸神 魔法斗士
Do you have any idea how totally insane you sound?
你知道你听起来有多疯狂吗？
I know, it is a lot to take in, isn't it?
我知道, 这很难接受, 不是吗？
So why don't we have breakfast, take the day off and...
那么, 我们为什么不吃点早餐, 休息一天, 然后...
revisit this tomorrow. Yeah.
明天再看 嗯
Well, I am hungry, but...
我饿了, 但是...
A goddess's fate is on the line, but sure.
女神的命运岌岌可危, 但是好吧
Let's eat pancakes.
我们去吃煎饼吧
Yeah.
对
Get off my ring, you scum.
从我的擂台上滚开, 你这个人渣
Get out of my ring!
滚出我的擂台
You moron.
你个白痴
You were supposed to keep a low profile.
你应该保持低调
And I did.
我做到了
We need to shut this place down.
我们得把这地方关掉
- You don't get to decide that! - That's right. I do.
- 这不是你能决定的 - 没错 我可以
Guraad, come on.
古拉杜, 别
We have a great partnership.
我们合作得很好
Yes. We did.
是的 是的
How's the boy's Cosmo?
那小子的小宇宙怎么样？
It's legit.
很正宗
Good news. I've got a new deal for you.
好消息 我有一个新交易给你
No ring, no deal.
没有擂台, 就没有交易
All the better.
那就更好了
Nobody needs a loser who gets his ass kicked by a scrawny little kid.
没有人会需要一个 被一个小毛孩子打得屁滚尿流的失败者
He got a lucky break.
他很走运
No man gets lucky twice with Cassios.
没有人能在卡西欧士身上走运两次
I can beat anyone, anytime.
我随时都能击败任何人
Well, let's see if that's true.
让我们看看这是不是真的
Something wrong?
有什么问题吗？
I just don't know how you can breathe while you're eating like that.
我真不知道就你那种吃法怎么还能呼吸的
Where I come from, you eat as much as you can, when you can.
在我们那里, 有东西吃的时候, 能吃多少就吃多少
You never know where your next meal's coming from.
你永远不知道下一顿饭在哪里
You wouldn't understand.
你不会明白的
Rich girl.
富家千金
No, I wouldn't.
不, 我不会
But I'm sorry you had to live like that.
但我很遗憾你不得不那样生活
Sir. There's an urgent call.
先生 有紧急电话
Please excuse me.
请原谅
So...
所以...
How does it feel to be a goddess?
成为女神的感觉如何？
Well, I'm not a goddess yet.
好吧, 我还不是女神
Just Sienna.
只是沙织
But her Cosmo is getting stronger by the day,
但她的小宇宙一天比一天强大
and someday soon I will become Athena.
不久之后, 我将成为雅典娜
Most people would be excited
大多数人会感到兴奋
to have breakfast with a future goddess.
与未来的女神共进早餐
Guess I'm not most people, then.
看来我不是大多数人
Well, then maybe you should...
那么, 也许你应该...
Maybe I should what?
也许我应该什么？
You should back off.
你应该退后
Jeez, don't be so sensitive.
哎呀, 别这么敏感嘛
Just get away from me, okay?
离我远点, 好吗？
- Okay, I'm sorry. - Just get away...
- 好吧, 对不起 - 走开...
Hey!
嘿！
Dad!
爸爸
Hey!
嘿！
- Are you okay? - Wait!
- 你还好吗？ - 等等
What's going on?
怎么了？
She could kill you right now.
她现在就能杀了你
I'm here, sweetheart, just relax.
我在这里, 亲爱的, 放轻松
What just happened?
刚才发生了什么？
She bears a goddess's Cosmo in the body of a mortal.
她以凡人之躯承载着一个女神的小宇宙
When our sensors detect a potential Cosmo burst,
当我们的传感器检测到潜在的小宇宙爆发时
the building automatically blocks the signal.
建筑物就会自动屏蔽信号
It's the only way we can keep Sienna hidden from Guraad.
只有这样才能不让古拉杜发现沙织
Which is why I am stuck here like a prisoner.
这就是我像囚犯一样被困在这里的原因
Excuse me.
打扰一下
Wait. Wait, so... So you really are...?
等等, 那么...你真的是...
You really think this guy could beat the Pegasus Knight?
你真的认为这家伙能打败天马座圣斗士？
Perhaps. If we give him the prototype.
也许吧 如果我们给他一套暗黑圣衣的话
Next candidate?
下一个候选人？
You giving up already?
你已经放弃了？
What the hell are you made of?
你到底是什么做的？
Disengage.
别打了
We ain't done yet.
我们还没完呢
You made your point, Cassios.
你说得很清楚, 卡西欧士
You're a strong man.
你是个坚强的人
But you're just a man.
但你只是个人
I have a problem.
我有个麻烦
You met him in your ring.
你在你的擂台上见过他
The kid.
那个孩子
His power's a liability.
他的力量是个负担
Once he learns to control it, no living man will be able to stop him.
一旦他学会控制它, 任何活人都无法阻止他
What, you think I could, though?
怎么, 你觉得我可以吗？
You know, with your prototype thing?
穿上你那暗黑圣衣？
I have a good ear.
我的耳朵很灵
So, what's your price?
那么, 你想要多少钱？
Well, that depends.
那要看情况了
Can I kill him?
我能杀了他吗？
That's kind of the point.
这才是重点
I'll do it for free.
我免费帮你
- You all right? - I'm better.
- 你还好吗？ - 我好多了
- You? - I'm good. I guess.
- 你呢？ - 我很好 我想
It's just that I can't believe you really are a...
只是我不敢相信你真的是一个...
A goddess?
女神？
I'm never gonna call you that.
我永远不会那样叫你的
That's fine with me.
我没意见
So how do people usually react when they learn you're Athena?
那么, 当人们知道你是雅典娜时, 通常会有什么反应呢？
Varies.
各不相同
Like, the day after I was born, someone tried to kill me.
比如, 我出生的第二天, 就有人想杀我
No.
不
Not even you could annoy someone that much in just one day.
即使是你, 也不可能在一天之内就那样惹恼一个人
I was told a knight in gold armor gave his life to save mine.
他们告诉我, 一位穿着黄金圣衣的圣斗士为救我献出了生命
When they found him, he was still holding me in his arms.
当他们找到他时, 他还抱着我
Who found you? Alman?
谁找到你的？光政？
And Guraad.
还有古拉杜
Though she was a little more into the gold armor.
虽然她更喜欢黄金圣衣
Used it to develop technology far beyond anything you could imagine.
利用它开发出来的技术远远超出你的想象
Look at the bright side.
往好的方面看
Half your foster family is great.
你的寄养家庭至少有一半还不错
When Alman's around you, he almost looks like a real dad.
当光政在你身边时, 他几乎就像一个真正的父亲
Alman is my dad, and I love him more than anything in the world.
光政就是我的父亲, 我爱他胜过世界上的一切
Although that might be hard for you to understand, street boy.
虽然你可能很难理解, 街头小子
I do.
我能理解
I had someone like that once.
我曾经也有过这样的亲人
Your sister?
你姐姐？
What was she like?
她是个什么样的人？
She was kind.
她很善良
And strong.
也很强大
And protected me when I couldn't protect myself.
在我还不能保护自己的时候保护着我
And you won't stop until you find her.
不找到她, 你是不会罢休的
You really don't care that I've become your bodyguard, do you?
你真的不在乎我当不当你的保镖，是吗？
I will someday become Athena.
总有一天, 我会成为雅典娜
I don't have a choice.
我别无选择
But that doesn't mean you have to become the Pegasus Knight.
但这并不意味着你必须成为天马座圣斗士
Alman said it's my destiny.
光政说这是我的命运
Nobody's destiny is written in stone.
没有人的命运是一成不变的
Except yours.
除了你的
Your Cosmo bursts,
你的小宇宙爆发时
do they come with visions?
会有幻象出现吗？
You have visions too?
你也有幻象？
What does it matter?
这有什么意义吗？
Cosmo visions are a window into the universe.
小宇宙幻象是一扇通往宇宙的窗户
They can show us things.
可以向我们展示一些事情
So that Silver Knight your dad mentioned...?
你爸爸提到的那个白银圣斗士....？
- Who, Marin? - Marin.
- 谁, 魔铃？ - 魔铃
Do you think if he could teach me to control my Cosmo,
你觉得如果他能教我控制我的小宇宙的话
I could use it to find my sister?
我可以用它找到我姐姐吗？
Maybe.
也许吧
If that's what you want.
如果这就是你想要的
He's drained of Cosmo, Guraad.
他的小宇宙被吸干了, 古拉杜
Won't get another dose.
不用再来一轮了
The prototype procedure has started.
暗黑圣衣程序已启动
It'll be ready tomorrow.
明天就好了
Any issues?
有问题吗？
Just one.
只有一个
Why Cassios?
为什么是卡西欧士？
'Cause you failed.
因为你失败了
You know, the target was assisted by Alman Kido.
要知道, 目标有城户光政的协助
A personal bad penny.
私人旧债
Athena's growing stronger by the day,
雅典娜越来越强大了
and now she'll have the Pegasus Knight by her side.
现在, 她将由天马座圣斗士守护着
I reckon the boy's got some Cosmo. Doesn't mean he's a knight yet.
我觉得这孩子是有点小宇宙了 并不意味着他已经是圣斗士了
I don't need cold comfort, Nero.
我不需要冷冰冰的安慰, 尼禄
I need to know where on Earth Alman is hiding the girl.
我要知道光政到底把那女孩藏在哪儿了
So we can neutralize her before she becomes Athena
这样我们就能在她变成雅典娜并毁灭世界之前
and destroys the world.
解除她的威胁
Beats me.
难住我了
But you could always ask our prisoner.
不过, 你可以问问我们的囚犯
We have a prisoner?
我们抓了一个囚犯？
Hey!
嘿！
Hey, wait up.
嘿, 等等
Yeah?
怎么了？
I...I just figured you could focus more on your training if you weren't
我只是在想, 你应该可以更专注于你的训练
worried about where your next meal was coming from.
如果不用担心下一顿饭从哪里来的话
Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
I guess.
我猜也是
Seiya!
星矢
Time to go.
该走了
See you.
再见
Take a seat.
请坐
Don't get any big ideas.
不要想法太多
Goddesses don't have boyfriends.
女神不会有男朋友的
- How many dads does Sienna have? - Buckle up.
- 沙织小姐这是有几个爸爸啊？ - 系好安全带
Lunchbox?
午餐盒？
That's unusually kind of you.
你这是太好了啊
I just thought he might as well enjoy his last meal,
我只是想让他好好享受最后一餐
since Marin's probably gonna kill him anyway.
因为魔铃很可能会杀了他的
Right.
对
So where am I supposed to go?
那我该去哪儿？
Okay. Just drop me off up there.
好 就在那边把我放下来
Not how it works.
不是这样的
"Those who seek the master must do so on foot."
" 千里之行 始于足下"
What the hell am I doing here?
我到底在这里干什么？
I was wondering the same thing.
我也在想同样的问题
You must be Marin.
你一定是魔铃
- The Silver Knight. - You look surprised.
- 白银圣斗士 - 你看起来很惊讶
Yeah. No, I'm... I mean...
是的 不 我...我是说...
No offense, I thought you'd be a man.
无意冒犯, 我以为你是个男人
No offense taken.
没觉得冒犯
I thought the same of you.
我也是这么以为你的
What's the training schedule like here?
这里的训练安排是什么？
I only train knights.
我只训练圣斗士
I'm told I'm the Pegasus Knight.
据说我是天马座圣斗士
You're not the first boy with a pretty necklace to show up here.
你不是第一个带着漂亮项链出现在这里的男孩
Is there a test I can take or something?
有什么测试可以测测吗？
The Pegasus Knight is brave.
天马座圣斗士勇敢
Check.
对
Humble.
谦卑
Check.
对
And committed to protecting Athena with his life.
发誓用生命保护雅典娜
Okay, that's where this whole situation gets a little sticky.
好吧, 这就是情况变得有点棘手的地方
See, I lost my sister... Hey!
你看, 我失去了我的姐姐...嘿
I just got up here!
我才刚上来
I just got up here.
I'm not going down there.
我不会下去的
There's nothing for you here.
这里没有你要的东西
What are you? Like, a ninja?
你是什么人？忍者吗？
Listen, I only wanna find my sister. Sienna said you could help.
听着 我只想找到我姐姐 沙织小姐说你能帮忙
I knew a knight just like you.
我认识一个和你一样的圣斗士
He desired power for his own goals.
他渴望变强，只是为了实现自己的目标
- Which was? - The Phoenix.
- 哪个？ - 凤凰座
The most powerful of Athena's knights.
雅典娜最强大的圣斗士
You mean, aside from the Pegasus Knight.
你是说, 除了天马座圣斗士之外？
I'll have Mylock come get you in the morning.
我会让晨己明早来接你
No. Come on, I made it this far.
不, 拜托, 我好不容易才到这里的
And how far is that?
有多不容易？
Do you even know how far you need to go?
你知道自己还有多远的路要走吗？
Just give me one chance.
给我一个机会
If you can break this rock...
如果你能打破这块石头...
then you can be my student.
那么你就可以成为我的学生
Fair enough.
很公平
Where's the hammer?
锤子在哪？
Come on, I can't break a rock with my bare hands.
拜托, 我不可能赤手空拳打碎一块石头
A knight could.
圣斗士可以
You can't be serious.
你不是认真的吧
You're serious.
你是认真的
I told you, this was stupid!
我告诉过你, 这样太蠢了！
Your flesh, this rock, the stars in the sky,
你的肉体, 这块岩石, 天上的星辰
all things in the cosmos are made from the same atoms.
宇宙万物都是由相同的原子构成的
From the moment we are born, we all hold a Cosmo within ourselves.
从出生的那一刻起, 我们每个人的体内都有一个小宇宙
A knight can make it explode.
圣斗士可以让其爆发
And shatter the atoms of any object.
并粉碎任何物体的原子
How's that supposed to make any sense?
这怎么能说得通呢？
Focus.
集中注意力
Clear your mind.
理清思绪
Feel the Cosmo within you.
感受你体内的小宇宙
Seiya!
星矢!
This is stupid, it'll never work!
这太愚蠢了, 根本行不通！
Something clouded your focus at the last minute.
在最后关头, 你的注意力被什么东西遮住了
Figures. Guess I'm not the Pegasus Knight after all.
看出来了 估计我终究不是天马座圣斗士
No, you're not.
对, 你不是
But maybe you will be.
但也许你将来会是的
Are you ready to start your training?
你准备好开始训练了吗？
It's a good thing he didn't mind the permanent changes to his body.
好在他并不介意身体的永久性改变
- Well... - What?
- 呃 - 什么？
I might have forgotten to mention the permanent part to him.
我可能忘了跟他说永久性那部分
What the hell is this?
这是什么鬼东西？
What did you do? You made...
你做了什么？你把...
You made me a freaking cyborg!
你把我变成了一个他妈的机器人
What is that?
那是什么？
It's the curse of Athena.
这是雅典娜的诅咒
The war that awaits us is unlike any other before.
等待我们的是一场前所未有的战争
Our enemies are the gods themselves.
我们的敌人就是众神本身
We've all made sacrifices.
我们都做出了牺牲
But what is flesh in comparison to the power to crush the immortals?
但是, 与碾压众神的力量相比, 肉体又算得了什么呢？
A war with the gods, huh?
与众神开战？
There's only one person I wanna crush.
我只想搞死一个人
Well, that was a nice little show.
这真是一场精彩的小演出
Let's move on. We have bigger issues at hand.
先别管他 我们手头还有更大的问题
- Bigger than his ego? - Your prisoner.
- 比他的自负还大？ - 你的囚犯
He's a tough one. I can't get him to talk.
他是个硬骨头 我没法让他开口
- Any ideas? - Have you tried asking nicely?
- 有什么主意吗？ - 你试过友好一点地询问吗？
Let's get a baseline.
我们来摸下底
Show me what you know.
让我看看你有什么本事
You mean, fight you? Now?
你是说, 跟你打一架？现在？
You came here to train, yes?
你是来受训的, 是吗？
Is dancing all you can do?
你只会跳舞吗？
Shouldn't I have a weapon or something?
我是不是应该有个武器什么的？
Athena's knights wield no weapon.
雅典娜的圣斗士们从不拿武器
That sucks.
真菜
Okay, I felt that one.
好吧, 我体会到了
It wasn't a direct hit.
又没有直接击中你
How the hell'd you do that?
你是怎么做到的？
You want a weapon?
你想要武器吗？
Your Cosmo is your weapon.
你的小宇宙就是你的武器
Focus your energy,
集中精力
let it burn inside of you.
让它在你体内燃烧
Release it all at once.
一次性全部释放
Like a shooting star.
就像一颗流星
Felt more like a meteor shower to me.
我感觉更像是一场流星雨
So do I get to learn this meteor fist of yours?
那我能学学你这套流星拳吗？
You must...
必然的...
if you want to survive the battles that await you.
如果你想在等待着你的战斗中幸存的话
Sienna!
沙织
It's all right. It's all right.
没事了 没事的
I'm here. It's all right.
我在这 没事了
I had another vision. Bad one.
我又看到了一个幻象 很糟糕
It's okay, it's all gone now.
没关系, 现在都过去了
Dad...
爸爸...
How can you be so sure I'll grow up to protect the world?
你怎么能确定我长大后能保护这个世界？
You are the goddess of wisdom, remember?
你是智慧女神, 还记得吗？
And warfare.
还有战争女神
And you're my baby girl.
你是我的宝贝女儿
The most loving and stubborn.
最有爱心, 也最固执
Nothing could stop you from doing what's right.
没有什么能阻止你做正确的事
What did you see?
你看到了什么？
People... burning.
人....在燃烧
Cities in ruins.
废墟中的城市
Everything...
一切...
destroyed.
都被摧毁了
We won't let that happen, will we?
我们不会让这种事情发生的, 不是吗？
You don't understand. It was Athena.
你不明白 是雅典娜干的
She was doing it. I...
她正在动手 我...
I was doing it.
我正在动手
Visions are just... possibilities.
幻象只是...一种可能
Dad, I know you'd let the world burn to keep me safe...
爸爸 我知道你宁愿让世界毁灭 也要保护我的安全....
but what if that's not me anymore?
但如果那个人不再是我了呢？
Prove to me you're worthy. Focus.
向我证明你的价值 集中注意力
Is that all you've got?
你就这点本事？
Your body is here.
你的身体在这里
But your mind is elsewhere.
但你心思在别的地方
Seiya.
星矢
There's so many things I need to tell you.
我有很多事情要告诉你
I'm here to protect you.
我是来保护你的
Now stop my attack.
现在阻止我的攻击
You're failing.
你失败了
Was he a knight too?
他也是圣斗士吗？
The Pegasus?
天马座？
Mind and body must become one.
身心必须合一
A knight's power comes from within.
圣斗士的力量来自内心
You give up?
你投降了？
If you can't do this, you'll never be a knight.
如果你做不到这一点, 就永远当不了圣斗士
You give up?
你投降了？
How did you say you ended up here, again?
你说你是怎么到这里来的？
I didn't say. And it's none of your...
我没说 这不关你的...
Right, I'm not supposed to know. I know.
对 我不应该知道 我知道
My destiny is bound to this island.
我的命运与这座小岛紧紧相连
Well, that sounds like a lonely existence.
这听起来像是一种孤独的生活
But not one without purpose.
但也不是毫无使命的
You know, I...
你知道, 我...
I have a purpose too.
我也有自己的使命
To find my sister.
找到我姐姐
A knight should not mistake obsession for purpose.
圣斗士不应将痴迷误当成使命
I know there is pain in your past...
我知道你的过去很痛苦...
but beyond that pain, there lies your strength.
但在痛苦之外, 还有你的力量
Find it and the armor will accept you.
找到了, 圣衣就会接受你
This is what your sister would've wanted.
这是你姐姐想要的
Get some sleep.
好好睡一觉
I get it.
我明白了
You're tough.
你很强悍
You know, someone once taught me
有人曾经教过我
that all men, no matter how tough,
所有男人, 无论多么强悍
have something they fear.
都有他们害怕的东西
I wonder what it is a big man like you fears the most.
我很想知道像你这样的大块头最害怕什么
Who are you?
你是谁？
You have no idea what I'm capable of.
你根本不知道我的能耐
Make it stop.
让它停下来
Make it stop!
让它停下来！
Make it go away.
让它消失
Now...
现在...
would you mind telling me where I can find Alman Kido?
你能告诉我在哪里可以找到城户光政吗？
Make it stop!
让它停下来！
- This one's bigger than the last one. - And your Cosmo is stronger.
- 这个比上个大啊 - 你的小宇宙也更强了
Now, show me what you've learned.
现在, 让我看看你学到了点什么
You did it, Seiya.
你做到了, 星矢
The Pegasus armor is...
天马座圣衣是...
You can't use it. Only the Pegasus can.
你用不了的 只有天马座才可以
That's why you're coming with us.
这就是为什么你要跟我们走
Alman.
光政
He was a part of it.
他也参与了
He was there when Guraad took Patricia.
古拉杜抓走星华的时候, 他也在场
I want off this island.
我要离开这个岛
You are not ready.
你还没准备好
Your training is not over.
你的训练还没有结束
It is now.
现在结束了
Alman's been playing me for a fool!
光政把我当傻瓜耍
You must calm down.
你必须冷静下来
If your heart and mind aren't clear, the armor will reject you.
如果你的心智不清晰, 圣衣就会拒绝你
To hell with the armor!
让圣衣见鬼去吧
Seiya.
星矢
I don't care.
我不在乎
You can either kill me now...
你要么现在就杀了我...
or send me back.
要么就把我送回去
Let's go. One more round, guys.
我们走 再来一轮 伙计们
Come on.
来吧
How's it coming along?
进展如何？
You want this to work, I need more time.
要想成功, 我需要更多时间
Be careful, you idiot!
小心点, 笨蛋
Yeah, running out of sparring partners. You care to join?
呃 没有陪练了 你想加入吗？
Oh, I'm sorry. Busy day.
哦 对不起 太忙了
Right, right. You're playing with your god-killing toy over here.
对 对 你在这玩你的弑神玩具呢
Yeah.
呃
So much trouble for one little girl.
一个小姑娘还用得着这么麻烦
You know, if you ask me,
要我说
I'd be more than happy to snap her neck the old-fashioned way.
我很乐意用老办法扭断她的脖子
Any damage to Sienna's body might awaken Athena's Cosmo within her.
沙织身体的任何损伤 都可能会唤醒她体内雅典娜的小宇宙
Yeah, I don't even know what that means.
是啊, 我都不知道那是什么意思
It means you can't dismantle a nuclear bomb by smashing it with a club.
意思就是 你拿棍棒敲两下就想拆除核弹 那是不可能的
I'd sure love to try.
我很想试试
It's not happening.
别做梦了
Make it work.
赶紧搞定
Alman!
光政
I know what you did!
我知道你干过什么！
- Come face me, you coward. - Stand down!
- 出来对质, 你个懦夫 - 退后
I'll handle this.
我来处理
- Seiya, please. - Alman!
- 星矢, 别 - 光政
Please calm down.
请冷静
Stand back!
退后
You can't hide from me.
你躲不了的
Seiya!
星矢
He took Patricia. He was in on it.
他带走了星华 他也参与了
There's more to it than that.
不止如此
No! No, you don't wanna do that.
不, 不, 你不会想这么做的
You don't understand.
你不明白
Come with me. I'll tell you what really happened to your sister.
跟我来 我会告诉你你姐姐到底发生了什么事
Sienna, you know the rules.
沙织小姐 你知道规矩的
You must not leave the mansion grounds.
你绝不能离开宅邸
You said you have answers.
你说你有答案
Hey!
嘿！
Alman was there when Guraad took Patricia. He was a part of it.
古拉杜抓走星华时 光政也在场 他也参与了
Tell me I'm wrong.
告诉我我错了
He did it because of me.
他是因为我才这么做的
When I was younger, I had no control at all.
我还小的时候, 根本无法控制自己
One night, my mom was holding me and I had a burst of Cosmo.
一天晚上, 妈妈抱着我, 我的小宇宙突然爆发了
I don't even know how it happened.
我甚至不知道这是怎么发生的
All I remember is she was holding me and I destroyed her arms.
我只记得当时她抱着我, 而我毁了她的手臂
And the next moment, she was dying and it was all my fault.
下一秒, 她就奄奄一息, 而这一切都是我的错
Alman used the power of the gold armor to save her,
光政用黄金圣衣的力量救了她
but ever since the accident, Guraad needs Cosmo to stay alive.
但自从事故发生后, 古拉杜就需要靠小宇宙来维持生命
So what? You've got plenty of it.
那又怎样？你不是有很多
Athena's Cosmo's too powerful. It would kill her.
雅典娜的小宇宙力量太强大了 会杀了她的
That's why she sought out kids like your sister.
这就是为什么她要抓像你姐姐这样的孩子
What did she do to Pat?
她对星华做了什么？
Your sister didn't have any Cosmo.
你姐姐没有小宇宙
Once Guraad figured that out, she let her go.
古拉杜明白这一点后, 就放她走了
But she sent her men to watch her.
但她派人监视着她
Guraad knew Patricia was hiding something.
古拉杜知道星华隐瞒着什么
Me.
我
That's why she never came back.
这就是为什么她再也没有回来
Look, I'm sorry, Seiya. If I knew, I...
对不起 星矢 如果我知道 我...
My mother was never the same after the incident.
事件发生后, 我的母亲完全变了一个人
She became convinced that Athena had returned to this world to end it.
她开始相信雅典娜重生就是为了结束这个世界
She was gonna kill me, so my father forced me into hiding.
她要杀了我, 所以我父亲只好带着我躲起来
And left Pat behind.
抛弃了星华
Your sister wasn't the only one.
你姐姐不是唯一一个
We left them all behind.
被我们抛弃的
How many kids did your family take?
你家劫走了多少孩子？
Our radar picked up Guraad's signature.
我们的雷达发现了古拉杜的踪迹
So it is happening.
终于来了
We don't stand a chance.
我们没有胜算的
You need to get out of here. I'll buy you as much time as I can.
你必须离开这里 我会尽可能多争取点时间
I'm not running from a fight.
我不会逃避战斗
Find Sienna.
找到沙织小姐
Protect her.
保护她
You're the only one I can trust.
你是我唯一可以信任的人
And, Mylock?
晨己
You've been a good friend.
你一直是个好朋友
Thank you.
谢谢
After Pat was taken, I ran away.
星华被抓走后, 我就跑了
All these years, I've never stopped looking for her.
这些年来, 我从未停止过寻找她
Turns out she was the one who was keeping away from me.
原来是她在躲着我
Your sister sacrificed herself
你姐姐牺牲自己
because she believed in what you really are.
因为她相信你的天命所归
I never asked to be a knight.
我从没想过要成为圣斗士
I only wanted to be with Pat.
我只想和星华在一起
You think I wanted any of this?
你以为我想要这些吗？
Sometimes I feel like I'm a guest in my own body.
有时候, 我觉得我就像是自己身体里的客人
In time, I thought I'd learn to control it.
假以时日, 我一定会学会控制它
But you're fighting it.
但你还在努力
What if my mother was right?
如果我母亲是对的呢？
What if I was only born to bring ruin and misery into this world?
如果我的出生只是为了给这个世界带来毁灭和痛苦呢？
That's not who you are.
你不是这样的人
How do you know?
你怎么知道？
I guess I just know.
我想我就是知道
I need you to promise me...
我需要你答应我...
if things go wrong...
如果出了差错...
if, in the end, I become a goddess of war and I can't control my powers...
如果最后我成为了战争女神, 却无法控制自己的力量....
you will stop me, at all costs.
你要阻止我 不惜一切代价
- You don't mean... - Just promise me, please.
- 你不是说... - 答应我, 求你了
That's my mother.
那是我妈妈
Sienna, wait, you can't go back!
沙织小姐 等等 你不能回去
- You're the one she's after. - I have to help my father.
- 你才是她的目标 - 我得帮我父亲
Okay.
好的
I'm with you.
我支持你
For now.
暂时
Shut it! Shut it!
关上！关上！
Hold.
守好
Don't let them through!
别让他们过去
No! No...!
不
It's clear.
安全了
Where's Seiya?
星矢呢？
And whatever her name is?
还有那个谁来着？
Sienna is not here, but I am willing to make a deal.
沙织不在, 但我愿意做个交易
Old man, you are in no position to be making deals.
老头, 你没有资格做交易
Wait outside, Cassios.
在外面等着, 卡西欧士
- Are you serious? - Out!
- 你是认真的吗？ - 出去
Hey!
嘿！
I really need to get to this ship.
我真的需要去这艘船
Glad you understand.
很高兴你们能理解
How do you like my special bullets?
喜欢我的特制子弹吗？
Let's make this easy, shall we?
让我们别搞得太复杂, 好吗？
Just tell me where she is.
直接告诉我她在哪儿吧
Straight to business, then.
直奔主题 呃
What do you expect, after she almost killed me?
她差点杀了我, 你还能指望什么？
That was an accident and you know it.
那是个意外, 你知道的
You can't blame Sienna for it.
这不能怪沙织
Oh, I never blamed Sienna.
我从没责怪过沙织
I blamed you, Alman,
我怪你, 光政
for leaving me to make all the hard choices.
怪你让我来做所有艰难的选择
How is murdering a little girl even a choice?
谋杀一个小女孩算什么选择？
She's a sword of Damocles hanging over all of us.
她是一把悬在我们所有人头上的达摩克利斯之剑
- She's your daughter. - We never had a daughter!
- 她是你女儿 - 我们没有女儿
What we had was an agreement, remember?
我们商量好了的, 记得吗？
That when she'd go out of control, we'd do whatever had to be done together.
当她失去控制时，我们会一起做任何必须做的事情
Sienna was entrusted to me.
沙织被托付给我
I'm responsible for her.
我要对她负责
I believe in her.
我相信她
You must believe in our child too.
你也应该信任我们的孩子
What about all the children you took to make these?
那些被你带走去做这个的孩子们怎么办？
Weren't you responsible for them?
你不用对他们负责吗？
It was the only way to save you.
这是拯救你的唯一办法
And now I must save the rest of us from her.
现在, 我必须从她手中拯救我们其他人
Speaking of the devil.
说曹操 曹操到
Dad?
爸？
I didn't want to do this, but I won't let you hurt her.
我也不想这么做, 但我不会让你伤害她
I know.
我知道
Cassios!
卡西欧士
Enough!
够了
Get me the girl. You can do what you want with the boy.
把女孩带给我 你想怎么处置那男孩都行
Seiya!
星矢
We need to go.
我们得走了
Hey there. I'm gonna take the girl now.
你们好 我要带走那个女孩
But first, I want you.
但首先, 我要杀了你
Let's end this now.
让我们现在做个了结吧
- No, Seiya. Don't. - It's okay.
- 不 星矢 别 - 没事的
I've got the armor.
我有圣衣
Any time now.
快点啊
Sienna, stay back!
沙织小姐 退后
Things have changed, kid.
今非昔比了, 小子
Face it, you don't have what it takes.
面对现实吧, 你不具备这样的能力
I loved these glasses.
我喜欢这副眼镜
Stop! Stop!
住手！住手
You've won. I'm coming with you. Let him go.
你赢了 我跟你走 放了他
You're coming with me anyway.
反正你也要跟我走
Rescue on the way, kids.
救援马上就到, 孩子们
I'm sorry,
对不起
but I'm taking you down with me.
但我要带你一起下去
Go! Go! Go!
快走
No.
不
It's ready.
准备好了
Give me a minute.
给我一分钟
Leave.
走开
You must think I'm the worst mother in the world.
你一定认为我是世界上最糟糕的母亲
You... You killed Father.
你...你杀了父亲
Alman chose his own way,
光政选择了自己了断
and left me to clean up his mess, as always.
然后让我来收拾他的烂摊子 一如既往
Athena's Cosmo is too strong.
雅典娜的小宇宙太强大了
It won't fix you.
救不了你的
I know.
我知道
Yeah. I gave up on fixing this body a long time ago.
是啊, 我早就放弃修复这具躯体了
We both have a bomb ticking inside.
我们的体内都有一颗炸弹在滴答作响
Except yours is gonna be so much louder if we let it go off.
只不过如果任由它爆炸, 你的那个声音会更大
I know I'm doing the right thing.
我知道我做得对
I just wanted you to know it doesn't make it any easier.
我只是想让你知道, 这并不会让你变得好受一点点
Will it hurt much?
会很疼吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
We need to start.
我们要开始了
Do it.
动手吧
能量消耗
Sienna...
沙织小姐...
That ain't gonna help, kiddo.
那没用的, 孩子
I let her get taken.
我看着她被抓走了
I failed.
我失败了
We all did.
我们都是
I was supposed to protect her.
我本该保护她
Things don't always work out the way we expect them to.
事情并不总是如我们所愿
Come on, Seiya.
来吧, 星矢
Marin.
魔铃
You were right about me.
你对我的看法是对的
I failed.
我失败了
I'm not a knight.
我不是圣斗士
I couldn't save her.
我救不了她
A knight should not mistake obsession for purpose.
圣斗士不应将痴迷误当成使命
Seiya, focus.
星矢, 集中注意力
Who is it that you're trying to save?
你拼命想要救的是谁？
Pat.
星华
What does this...?
这是什么....？
Who are you really trying to save?
你真正想救的到底是谁？
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I know.
我知道
It's okay.
没关系
It wasn't your fault.
这不是你的错
Okay.
好的
I'll bring her back.
我会带她回来的
I promise.
我保证
Okay.
好的
Let's go get Sienna back.
我们去把沙织小姐救回来
How long will it take?
需要多长时间？
To kill a god? Good question.
杀死一个神？问得好
We're about to find out.
我们马上就知道了
Oh, boy. They got us on radar.
天啊 我们被雷达发现了
- What? - Get ready.
- 什么？ - 准备好
For what?
准备什么？
I can get you close, but I can't land.
我可以让你靠近点, 但我没办法着陆
Parachute?
降落伞？
Who says you're not funny?
谁说你不搞笑的？
It's now or never!
机不可失, 时不再来！
Open the doors.
开门
Get yourself out of here!
快离开这里
Godspeed, kiddo.
祝你好运, 孩子
- Out of the way. - Hey!
- 别挡路 - 嘿
He's mine.
他是我的
Big deal. You know how to glow.
好大牌 你是懂抢镜的
Step aside, Cassios, if you don't wanna get hurt.
靠边站 卡西欧士 如果你不想受伤的话
Hurt?
受伤？
You should've died when you had the chance.
你有机会的时候真应该死了算了
What was it that you said, Cassios?
你说过什么来着, 卡西欧士？
Right.
对了
Oh, no.
哦, 不
Things have changed.
今非昔比了
Finally, the goddess Athena reveals herself.
终于, 雅典娜女神现身了
You must believe in our child too.
你也该信任我们的孩子
Stop! Stop the procedure!
停止！停止程序！
It'll be over soon.
很快就结束了
Now!
现在
We are not stopping!
我们不会停的！
Get out of my way.
让开
Guards!
警卫
Your services are no longer required.
不需要你的服务了
There's no stopping it now.
现在已经停不下来了
In moments, she'll be nothing but a memory.
顷刻间, 她将只剩下回忆
Kill him!
杀了他
You said it yourself, Guraad.
你自己说的, 古拉杜
When one goes to war with the gods, sacrifices must be made.
当一个人与众神开战时, 必须做出牺牲
There must be another way to protect humanity.
一定还有其他方法可以保护人类
Protect humanity?
保护人类？
Is that what you think you're doing?
这就是你以为你在做的事情？
Killing Athena was only half of the battle.
杀死雅典娜 战斗才进行了一半
This is the other half.
这是另一半
The gold armor.
黄金圣衣
Can't let you do that.
不能让你这么做
Thought you were the only knight in town?
你以为你是这里唯一的圣斗士吗？
You gotta get out of the way.
你最好把路让开
Sienna!
沙织
You're no match for the Phoenix.
你不是凤凰座的对手
Why do you try so hard?
你为什么这么拼命？
She's not worth it.
她不值得
She's not even human.
她甚至不是人类
Sienna's not a god of war.
沙织不是战争之神
I don't care what kind of god she is.
我不管她是什么样的神
Man needs no gods!
人类不需要神明！
You don't know when to quit.
你不知道什么时候该放弃
People keep telling me that.
人们老是这么说我
Stop, you fool!
住手, 你这个傻瓜！
Sienna!
沙织小姐
Listen to me! That's not your friend anymore!
听我说 那不再是你的朋友了
She's become the goddess of war.
她成了战争女神
We have to stop her!
我们必须阻止她！
Seiya.
星矢
I'm losing control.
我失控了
I don't think I can hold her back much longer.
我想我再也不能拖住她了
You can't save me,
你救不了我
but you can stop Athena.
但你可以阻止雅典娜
You must do it now.
你必须现在就动手
At all costs.
不惜一切代价
Sienna...
沙织小姐...
you're not a goddess of war.
你不是战争女神
No one's destiny...
没有人的命运...
is written in stone.
是一成不变的
Not even yours.
你的也不行
The guardian of mankind...
人类的守护神
or a petulant jerk...
或是一个傲娇鬼...
whatever you choose to be, I'll never give up on you.
无论你选择做哪一个, 我都不会放弃你
Seiya.
星矢
What? Why?
啥？为什么？
- What was that for? - Who's the petulant jerk?
- 这是干什么？ - 谁是傲娇鬼？
Oh, my...
哦, 我的...
Okay.
好的
- Get up. - Okay.
- 起来 - 好的
Let's get out of here.
我们走吧
Wait.
等等
I'm sorry.
对不起
I was wrong about you.
我看错你了
I wasn't so sure myself for a very long time.
很长时间里, 我自己也不太确定
You didn't have to do that.
你没必要这么做
Yes, I did.
有必要
Did I do this?
这是我干的吗？
Mylock!
晨己
Sienna!
沙织小姐
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
I'm okay.
我没事
Glad you made it, Seiya.
很高兴你做到了, 星矢
You too.
你也一样
So, boss...
那么, 老板...
what do we do now?
我们现在该怎么办？
Athena's awakening is a sign the old gods will soon return and try to start a war.
雅典娜的觉醒预示着旧神即将回归, 并试图发动战争
We need to gather all the Knights of the Zodiac to stop them.
我们需要召集所有黄道十二宫的圣斗士来阻止他们
I'm at your service, my lord.
愿为您效劳, 我的主人
Stop. Don't call me that.
少来 别这么叫我
Whatever you say, princess.
随你怎么说 公主
No. And definitely not that.
不, 千万别叫我这个
Before we gather the knights, there's something else we need to do.
在召集圣斗士之前 我们还有一件事要做
What's that?
那是什么？
It's time to find Patricia.
是时候去找到星华了
Thank you.
谢谢
It's the least a goddess could do.
这是女神最起码应该做的
《圣斗士星矢》
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的